Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- WRITINGS
  - To Be God's Own People (I Peter 2:9-10) (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - The Search (Matthew 13:45-46) (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Jan 18, 1976 - July 4, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - The Trumpet of Conscience (Isaiah 58:1) (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Aglow with the Spirit (Romans 12:11) (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Who is Number One? (Luke 13:30) (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - October 17, 1976 - December 26, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Renewal of the Basic Self (Romans 12:2) (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - The Challenge of Adversity (Proverbs 24:10) (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Untitled Speech to the Metropolitan Board of Education (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Towards the Restoration of Hope (Luke 1:49-50) (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - February 20, 1977 - May 22, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - When History Speaks Aright (Job 8:8) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Salute to Black Educational Leadership (honoring Walter Strother Davis) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Eulogy for Mr. James N. Lemons (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - The Evangelism of Defiance (Mark 2:17) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - June 5, 1977 - December 25, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - To Be Sent Out to Preach (Mark 3:14-15) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - How to Live Life (Acts 1:8) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - A Sense of the Vital (Philippians 1:1-11) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - On Seeing Strange Things (Luke 5:26) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - A Subjective Sense of History (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - And on Earth - Peace (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - February 5, 1978 - December 31, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Directions for the Man of God (I Timothy 6:11-12) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - The Internal Audit (I Corinthians 11:28) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - On Higher Ground (Matthew 5:1-5) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - And Yet... (address to Commission on Faith and Order) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Faith and Order in Bangalore: 1978 (I Peter 3:15; John 17:20-21) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - The Black Church and the Education of Blacks (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - The Wilderness Experience (Mark 1:12-13) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Human Need and the Divine Resource (Psalms 107:2) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - January 13, 1979 - August 26, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Resolution on Human Rights (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Quest for the High Encounter (John 12:20-21) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - On Stirring the City (Matthew 21:10-11) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Response to the National Council of Christians and Jews Award (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Faith's Unsung Heroes (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - The Failure of the Average (Matthew 5:47) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Now You Are God's People (I Peter 2:9-10) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - September 16, 1979 - December 30, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Goal: Generation of the Upright Will Be Blessed (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Assessment and Hope (Mark 12:34) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Address Delivered to the Annual Convocation of the National Conference of Black Churchmen, Inc. (1979) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - His Story in Our History (I Peter 1:23-25) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Positive Reflection (Psalms 126:3) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Untitled Notes (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - March 18, 1980 - March 22, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - They Who Preach: The Black Preacher Prophet (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Ministers Addressing the Issues of the Eighties: A Challenge for Social Responsibility (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - All in the Family (I Timothy 5:1-2) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - To Gather the Young (Isaiah 40:11) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Transgressors without Shame (Jeremiah 6:15) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - April 12, 1981 - December 13, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Cry of the Children (Matthew 21:15-16) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Flowers Appear (Solomon 2:11-12) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - If God Is For Us (Romans 8:31-32) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - There Is a Lad Here (John 6:9) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Our Family in the Faith (Galatians 6:10) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Futility of Anxiety (Matthew 6:25; Luke 12:25) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Kingdom without End (Luke 1:26-38) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - April 18, 1982 - June 13, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - God of Our Weary Years (Psalm 107:6) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Cry for the Children (Luke 23:28) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Social Crisis Preaching: Lecture I (1983) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Social Crisis Preaching: Lecture II (1983) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Social Crisis Preaching: Lecture III (1983) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Social Crisis Preaching: Lecture IV (1983) (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Sermons from Biblical Texts (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Genesis (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Forecast - Partly Clear (Genesis 9:13) (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Old Wells for a New Generation (Genesis 26:18) (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - God Is Here - Let's Celebrate (Genesis 28:16-17) (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Exodus (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - A Faith for Those Who Are Trapped (Exodus 14:9-25) (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Joshua (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - The Creative Presence (Joshua 1:5-9) The Righteous Marching (Joshua 6:20) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - I Samuel (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - God's Call for Action (I Samuel 2:3) (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Ezra (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - And Yet, It is Not Finished (title card only, Ezra 5:16) (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - II Chronicles (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - In A New House (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Proverbs (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - The Fruit of Her Hands (Proverbs 31:30-31) (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Ecclesiastes (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - The Now Generation Tomorrow (Ecclesiastes 11:9; 12:1-8; 13-14) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Jeremiah Something Old for the New (Jeremiah 6:16) (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Jeremiah (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - The Tragedy of Unfulfilled Promise (Jeremiah 8:20) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Jeremiah (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - We Seek a City (Jeremiah 50:5) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Job. Title card only, listing: (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - When History Speaks Aright (Job 8:8) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Songs in the Night (Job 35:9-10) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Voice of the Whirlwind (Job 38) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - The Deeper Response (Job 38:6) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Response to the Divine Encounter (Job 42:5) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ezekiel (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Twentieth Century Prophets (Ezekiel 3:16-31) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Isaiah (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - That Your Soul May Live (Isaiah 55:3) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - When the Light Comes (Isaiah 60:1-4) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Psalms (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - God Bless the Moon and God Bless Me (Psalms 8) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - To Live in His World (Psalms 24:1-2) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Quest for the Way (Psalms 25) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - A Religion That Expands (Psalms 31:8) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - The Waiting Game (Psalms 62) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - When God Arises (Psalms 68:1) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Let Us Sing a New Song (Psalms 98:1) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - The Religion of Gratitude (Psalms 100:4) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Psalms (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Christian Youth and the Quest for Freshness (Psalms 110:3) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Goal: Generation of the Upright Will Be Blessed (Psalms 112:2) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - What Shall I Render? (Psalms 116:2) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - At This Point in Time (Psalms 118:24) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - God Our Help (Psalms 121:1-2) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - The Joyful Procession (Psalms 122:1-2) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - For the Sake of the House (Psalms 122:9) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - We Are a Reverent People (Psalms 124:8) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Positive Reflections (Psalms 126:3) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Light through a Dark Window (Psalms 137:3) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - To Be Known of God (Psalms 139:1-6) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Great is the Lord (Psalms 145:3) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Grass upon the Mountains (Psalms 146:8) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Matthew (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - The Peace Makers (Matthew 5:1-9) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - How to See God (Matthew 5:8) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Where the Saints Have Trod (Matthew 5:10-16) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - To Dispel the Darkness (Matthew 5:14-16) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Beyond Affirmative Action (Matthew 5:20) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - The Relevant Extremist (Matthew 5:20) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - The Elusive Ideal (Matthew 5:38-48) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Love and the Weather (Matthew 5:43-45) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Hatred Meets Militant Love (Matthew 5:43-47) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Life's Narrow Gate (Matthew 7:14) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - The Temptation to Tune Jesus Out (Matthew 11:2-3) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Matthew (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - How Deep Are Your Roots? (Matthew 13:1-6) (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - The Search (Matthew 13:45-46) (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - The Importance of Children (Matthew 18:10) (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - On Stirring the City (Matthew 21:10-11) (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Matthew (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Unconditional Surrender (Matthew 22:37-40) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Conspiracy (Matthew 26:3-5; 14-16) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Introspection (Matthew 26:22) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Time of Joy and Fear (Matthew 28:1-10) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Time of Joy and Fear (Matthew 28:8) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Mark (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - To Touch and to Heal (Mark 1:40-45) (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Mark (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - To Cure the Paralysis (Mark 2:10-11) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - To Be Sent Out to Preach (Mark 2:13-19) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - The Evangelism of Defiance (Mark 2:17) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - The New Challenge (Mark 2:22) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - A Father's Compulsory Burden (Mark 15:21) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Pot (Mark 15:22-32) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Luke (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - The Unfaded Rose (Luke 1:31-33) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Getting Ready for Christmas (Luke 1:46-55) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - The Wonder of Christmas (Luke 2:18) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Jesus: The Child (Luke 2:49) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Luke (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - The Harmonies of Liberty (Luke 4:18) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - To Cure the Blindness (Luke 4:18) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - The Urgency of Depth (Luke 5:4) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - On Choosing the Good Portion (Luke 10:38-42) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - The Persistent Cry of Human Need (Luke 18:38-39 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - To Celebrate, to Cry, and to Act (Luke 19:28-46) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Jubilation and Judgment (Luke 19:37-46) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - This is the City (Luke 19:41) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Guilty (Luke 22:54-62) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Insecurity Meets Security (Luke 22:54-62; 23:8-11) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Dissent (Luke 23:1-12) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Father Forgive Them - And Us (Luke 23:32-38) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - John (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Power to Become (John 1:1-13) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Unrealized Potential (John 1:4) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - The Secret of Significance (John 1:6-8) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Authority Meets Power (John 10:15-18; 19:5-11) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Humble (John 13:1-9) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Humble? (John 13:6-9) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Curious (John 13:18-26) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Shaky Commitment (John 13:37) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Fear Meets Courage (John 14:1-4, 27) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Growing in Unity (John 17:1-11) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Prayer for the Church (John 17:20-21) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Execution (John 19:5-6) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Woman, Behold Your Son (John 19:25-29) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Acts (title card only) (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Romans (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - I Heard the Preaching of the Elder (Romans 10:14-15) (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - I Corinthians (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - In God's Garden (I Corinthians 3:4-9) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - The Wisdom of Becoming a Fool (I Corinthians 3:18) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - On Remembering Jesus (I Corinthians 11:24) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - The Internal Audit (I Corinthians 11:28) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Towards a Mature Faith (I Corinthians 13:11) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - On Becoming Yes Men (I Corinthians 1:19) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - II Corinthians (title card only) (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Ephesians (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - The Unbroken Line (Ephesians 2:19-22) (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Beyond the Tears (Ephesians 3-4) (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - One Body, One Spirit, One Hope (Ephesians 4:4) (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Philippians (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Thank God for the Church (Philippians 1:3) (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Discerning the Urgent (Philippians 1:9-10) (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - I Recommend Jesus (Philippians 2:9-11) (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - On Discerning the Garbage (Philippians 3:8-9) (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Colossians (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - To Be Mature in Christ (Colossians 1:28) (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - James (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Wanted: Men of Action (James 1:16-27) (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - No Shadow of Turning (James 1:17) (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - I Peter (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - People of God - Yes! (I Peter 2:9-10) (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - I John (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Jude (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Clouds without Water (Jude 12) (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Revelation (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Challenge for the Church (Revelation 2:1-7) (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - The Bright Morning Star (Revelation 22:16) (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Sermon Outlines on Church Bulletins, 1974-1983 and undated
  - November 9, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - An Angry Christ (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Judean Newscast (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Something Within (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Ride On, Conquering King (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Alone But Not Lonely (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Route to the Kingdom (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Victory through Christ (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - When Dreams Are Lost (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Song of Triumph (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Upper Room: Place of Guilt and Grace (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Beside the Still Waters (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - For His Name's Sake (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Valley of the Shadow (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Formula for Acceptable Religion (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Speaks to the Twisted Age (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - What Manner of Men? (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Advertisement for the Divine (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - On Becoming God's People (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Perils of Piety (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Creative Crisis (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - On the Profession of Our Faith (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Youth and the Challenge of the Church (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Worship and the Stewardship of Singing (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Toward the Feminine Potential (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Myth of Neutrality (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - January 2, 1966 - November 27, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Strength to Match Our Days (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Tragedy of Unreadiness (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Cry from the Streets (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Pious Perjury (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Christ of Experience (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Lord God Omnipotent Reigneth (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - There Will Be a Tomorrow (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Gospel According to Mothers (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Language of the Days (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Harsh Side of Love (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Loving the Unlovely (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Right Kind of Radical (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Quest for Moral Stability (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Mixing Religion and Business (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Beyond Bread (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Quest for Inner Unity (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Songs of the Stars (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Reflections of Departing Worshippers (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - January 1, 1967 - December 31, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Courage to Be Contemporary (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Youth and the Issues of Religion and Race (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Hold On! (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - When Man Has Reached His Extreme (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Bearers of the Light (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Thy Name to Sing (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Tragedy of the Unexcited (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Towards Valid Priorities (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - When Hope Rides on Fragments (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Discerning the Urgent (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Love and Fire (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Voice of Authority (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Reconciliation: Man Size Job (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - One Body.. .One Spirit.. .One Hope (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Hope in Swaddling Clothes (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Beyond the Tears (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Great is the Lord (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dare to be Different - When Necessary (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Devil Tried to Make Me Do It (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1972: Light and Shadows (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - January 7, 1973 - March 24, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - And He Shall Be Like a Tree (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - King's Way (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Towards Stubborn Expectancy (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - From Tears to Joy (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - March on Fear (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Tragedy of Counterfeit Wisdom (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Unfading Light (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Primacy of Surrender (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - If This Be of God (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - A New Day and a New Song (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - To Be the Church in Critical Times (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Christmas Dream (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - To Seek and to Find (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - At This Point in Time (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - God is Here - Let's Celebrate (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - When God Walks (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - To Be Known of God (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - May 5, 1974 - September 21, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Agenda for the Condemned (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Woman, Behold Your Son (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Unhealed Wounds (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Forecast - Partly Clear (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Life Before Death (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - When the Best Men Flee (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Your Son Shall Live! (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Yes, Lord! (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - A Joyful Noise - In Times Like These! (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Tragedy of Saying No to God (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Journey to Christmas and Beyond (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Waiting Game (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Religion of Gratitude (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Plea of a Zealous Mother (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Answer, My Friend, Is Blowing in the Wind (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Good News for Difficult Times (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Human Crisis and God's Timetable (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Voice of Authority in Troubled Times (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Healing Touch (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Transcending the Barriers (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - October 5, 1975 - December 26, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Something Old for the New (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - The Bright Morning Star (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Out of the Past with Pride (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Out of the Past with Pride - Into the Future with Hope (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Trumpet of Conscience (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Faith and Fortitude for the Future (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Man Wanted (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - God's Call for Action (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Aglow with the Spirit (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Life's Critical Question (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Cry of the Children (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Who is Number One? (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Unified to Face New Experiences Creatively (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - On Seeing the Wind (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Whither Shall I Flee? (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - How to Love Life (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Do! (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - The Extravagance of Total Commitment (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - The Challenge of Adversity (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Towards the Restoration of Hope (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - January 16, 1977 - September 10, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Ultimate March (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Mystery of the Weeds (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Unbroken Line (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Legacy of Love (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Call and Response of Faith (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - To Cure the Paralysis (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - More Than Bread (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - To Be Sent Out to Preach (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Stretch Out Your Hand (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - A Sense of the Vital (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - To Go Out in Joy (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - People of God - Believing (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - No Mighty Work (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - On Seeing Strange Things (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - And on Earth - Peace (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - On Discerning the Garbage (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Directions for the Man of God (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Deep is the Hunger (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Relevance of Mercy (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - How to See God Tomorrow's Hope Today (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - October 1, 1978 - September 30, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Committed: To Witness, to Serve, to Love (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Starting Place (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Charge to Youth (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Wilderness Experience (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - He Who Is Mighty (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Vital Promise! (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - From the Snare of the Fowler (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Serenity (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Love (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Surrender (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Importance of Children (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - A Father's Compulsory Burden (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - On Remembering Jesus (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Linking the Generations (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Faith's Unsung Heroes (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Keeping Life in Proportion (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Now You Are God's People (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Relevance of Mystery (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Goal: Generation of the Upright (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Determined Journey (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Assessment and Hope (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - October 7, 1979 - September 20, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Word of Power (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Blessing of Security (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Gift and Gifts of Christmas (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Positive Reflection (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Facing the '80s with Hope (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Life's Narrow Gate (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Alternating Tides of Living (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Silence of Disappointment (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Silence of Defiance (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Silence of Wounded Love (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Silence of Dignity (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Silence of Death (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - When the Darkness Is As Light (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - A Faith to Bridge the Gaps (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Divine Design and Human Disorder (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Of Fish and Snakes - Challenge to Fathers (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Turning the Upside-Down Right Side Up (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - If You Have Faith (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - No Sound of Weeping (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Full of the Spirit and Wisdom (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Let the People Say Amen (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - October 19, 1980 - September 20, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - To Touch the Sacred Fire (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - If the Lord Is with Us (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - The Negative Use of Thanksgiving (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - On Being Less Than God (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Hallelujah (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - When the Angels Went Away (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Voice From the Mountain (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - To Gather the Young (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Transgressor's Shame (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Cry of the Children (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - The Flowers Appear (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - If God Is For Us (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - There is a Lad Here (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Our Family in the Faith (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - For By Your Word (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - When the Light is Darkness (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - The Word of God is Unbound (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Called to Maladjustment (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Treasures New and Old (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - The Divine Assignment (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - October 18, 1981 - March 14, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - When Loyalty Is Tested (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - The Futility of Anxiety (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Failure of the Successful (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - The Anger of Love (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Custodians of the Mystery (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Prayer for the Church (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - The Divine Trailblazer (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Tampering with the Eternal (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Following the Good Example (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - March 28, 1982 - September 4, 1983, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - The Persistent Cry of Human Need (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Toward the Dawn (Box 26, Folder 12)